Guide to the Chilean zine collection M2094 M2094
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Chilean zine collection
circa 2009-2016
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
M2094
3.75 Linear Feet (9 manuscript boxes)
Content Description
Hundreds of zines from independent artists and publishers with a punk literary aesthetic. The zines are a platform to comment on social/political/economic injustices.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Note that material must be requested at least 36 hours in advance of intended use.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This collection was purchased by Stanford University, Special collections in 2015 and 2016. Accessions 2015-126 and 2016-149.
- Wackala, 1-2 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Calma resonante, 1-2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Se me escapa el corazón (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Tinta negra, 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Adentro, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Zink, 1-3 (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
- Zink: perros salvajes, 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Morder (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Sigue al Pato Cojo, julio 2013 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Los increíbles aventuras de un comiquero, 1, 3 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Módulo de prueba, mayo 2014 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Otk (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Comic underground (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Melodia, enero 2013 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- La vida en cómic, diciembre 2015 [y otro sin fecha] (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Convocatoria acéfala: 34 ilustraciones sin cabeza (Box 1, Folder 17)
- El abandono de Cristo (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Tortilla guerrilla, octubre 2013 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Flexiboy, noviembre 2013 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- R3gio, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Deograba, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Ciudades convertidas en selvas, 3 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Fanzine amor/odio, marzo 2014 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Esto cabría en 1.44 MB (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Escupitojo, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Agreste (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Casa tomada (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Friolera fanzine, 1 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Fanzine pirata, 1-2 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- E (Box 2, Folder 12)
- El niño que quería volar (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Amateur, 1 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Nuevo cereal de CD (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Lo que creíamos de chicos (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Cosas que me caen mal. (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Cosas que no entiendo (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Fititui, 2, 4, 7, 9 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Llave del sol (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Pandemia: historias olvidadas, 1-8 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Pandemia, octubre 2013, mayo 2014 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Mortus calavera, 1-7 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Mortus calavera, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- La mesa está servida: la colección completa y definitiva de los fanzines más intergalácticos (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Soledad, 1-3 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- En búsqueda de Charizad (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Fanzine jengibre, febrero 2015 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Fanzine interactivo (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Un regalo para Elena (Box 3, Folder 6)
- 2my10. el mundo de oso, junio 2010 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- ¿Fanzine? (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Princesa pía (Box 3, Folder 9)
- El fanzine mágico (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Tormentas (Box 3, Folder 11)
- [Title illegible]. Artist: Laese (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Cinema Bobo, 1 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Los videos favoritos de YouTube (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Bangkok (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Trompeta nuclear (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Hijos de Bostezo, 1-4 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- ¿Que pasó hace 24 hrs? (Box 3, Folder 18)
- El diario de Ana Funk (Box 3, Folder 19)
- The galaxy integirl (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Sueños (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Taller de fanzines de express, junio 2012 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Cazuela de gallina (Box 3, Folder 23)
- 3 1/2, julio 2013 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- El festín en el paraíso, diciembre 2014 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Palitos, diciembre 2014 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Hosco, diciembre 2014 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Brígida y Abdón; la blognovela, 2011-2012 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- ¡Hey, hagamos fanzines!, febrero 2015 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Trolley (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Serendipia (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Duro, 1-4 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Suculentas, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Neuronal ghost, abril 2015 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Nini, febrero 2015 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- De ríal jístory, 1 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Ni princesas ni barbies, 1-2 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Sin titulo, 2-14 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Una historia de liberacíon animal (Box 4, Folder 14)
- El puño de barrancas, 1 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Ecosidio (Box 4, Folder 16)
- La katanga, junio 2014, agosto 2014 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Oni, octubre 2013 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Era de noche, septiember 2-14 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- La zona extraña, diciembre 2014 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Noise makers, 1-3 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- El filo del norte, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Dei australis, noviembere 2013 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Kubrikc, 1-2 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Barandanga, 1 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Open Blonda (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Selecciones del fanzinoide, febrero 2015 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Plagio di plagio, 1 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Vizara con v de vaginoas, 2, 69 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Todos juntos hacia el abismo (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Las asquerosas y pagajosas aventuras de el Moco por ozyoso, 1 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Modernillo: folosofias varias, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Guau!, 1-3 y numero especial (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Desafio de dibujo por 30 días (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Grafolagnia pornozine (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Nunca cantar Victoria, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Fanzine familiar, marzo 2013 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Microperrajes (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Franstromers (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Jodorowsky y el cómic, noviembre 2014 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Me odias? (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Construcción (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Franzinoide miscelaneo (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Cielo (Box 5, Folder 14)
- La vida en código abierto (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Paf!, 1-3 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Falabras pavoritas (Box 5, Folder 17)
- El Profesor Leyton, 1 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- First contact (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Manzana (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Nací con esto, 1-2 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Maldita historieta sin sentido (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Otra maldita historieta sin sentido (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Bodeguero, enero 2015 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Excelso, febrero 2015 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Superfideos ovas (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Pobrecito mortal, 2 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Dispersiones y otras cosas (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Dron, 1 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Perdido, 1-3 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Papel ilustre, Imaginario Occipital, febrero de 2015, three issues of mayo de 2015, and abril de 2016 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Ovejas negras, Imaginario Occipital, diciembre 2015 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Super shile en: fuga'o, Imaginario Occipital (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Florece, Imaginario Occipital (Box 6, Folder 2)
- El show por el fanzine, Imaginario Occipital (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Niño perro, Imaginario Occipital (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Palpi animales, numero uno, Butzbo (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Glerp y Gur, Butzbo, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Manzana, Supem ilustraciones (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Afvera hay un jardin, Supnem, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- La tienda de animales, 2015, Supnem (Box 6, Folder 4)
- ¿Vamos?, Supnem (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Fanzine porque sí, Supnem, no. 1 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- No al embarazo infantil, Supnem, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Tetas tristes comics, Supnem, diciembre 2015 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Barandanga, n.3-5 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Triste y caliente, Nikolo (Box 6, Folder 7)
- [Lejos de la manada], Nikolo, Septiembre 2015 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Mujer planta, Daniela William, 2014 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Betleza cotidiana, Daniela William, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Paraisos, Daniela William, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Zagal, Pupa press, no. 1 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Cuadermos de viaje #3 - Taipei, Pupa presss, no 1, noviembre 2015 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Vivir mejor, Pupa press, no. 1, noviembre 2015 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Bodeguero, Francisco Visceral Rivera Rivera (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Excomunión, Francisco Visceral Rivera Rivera, numero 1, septiembre 2015 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- El abandono de cristo, Francisco Visceral Rivera Rivera (Box 6, Folder 11)
- El abandono de cristo, Francisco Visceral Rivera Rivera (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Excelso, Francisco Visceral Rivera Rivera, tomo 1 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Lesbilais, Tortilla perferica, Victoria Rubio, número 2, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- La lesbiana del zodiaco, Victoria Rubio, número 1, 2016 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Mierdal slug, La mano maestra (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Spider-woman visn san valentino, La mano maestra (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Freedom (Box 6, Folder 13)
- La guía para sobrevivir a la estupidez humana, Devil Katy (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Algo que decir, Devil Katy (Box 6, Folder 14)
- El fanzinoide, tomo 1-3 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- El fanzinoide presenta: 3 issues with titles: Peyote negro; Open blonda n. 4; La ultima bestia, all by Los fanzinoides (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Kafkaman, Los fanzinoides (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Sabiduriakata, Los fanzinoides, tomo 1: la experiencia (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Alta coleccion de dispersiones, Los fanzinoides (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Dispersiones y otras wevadas, [Los fanzinoides] (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Variette de dispersiones, los fanrinoides (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Bestiario, Green Sun,Los fanzinoides, n. 1-4 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Intenso, Rodrigo Duran Huidobro, Cayó la teja, 2016 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- De A2 es mejor, Rodrigo Duran Huidobro, Cayó la teja (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Tobías de sousa, Rodrigo Duran Huidobro, Cayó la teja (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Fanzineichon Rodrigo Duran Huidobro, Cayó la teja, 2016 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- El rey tiene cola, Rodrigo Duran Huidobro, Cayó la teja, Efímera cartonera (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Hámsteres, Rodrigo Duran Huidobro, Cayó la teja (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Hámsteres, Rodrigo Duran Huidobro, Cayó la teja (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Interestelar, Rodrigo Duran Huidobro, Cayó la teja, 2016 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Et Cetera, Felipín Bombín [Bizarro], 2015 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- El real maravilloso viaje de Pepe Sherazade, Felipe Bizarro (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Cejas de un hombre moderno, Felipe Bizarro (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Justicia verdadera, Felipe Bizarro, no.1 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Las aventuras del perro que cagaba pan, Felipe Bizarro (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Anverso, 3 numbers: Anverso ten-ten, Anverso vida, Anverso sofí, by Tue-Tue, Gonzalo Fernandéz (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Anverso ten-ten, Tue-Tue, Gonzalo Fernández (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Reverso, 3 numbers: Reverso muerte, Reverso tío, Reverso kai-kai, Tue-Tue, Gonzalo Fernández (Box 7, Folder 2)
- ¿Así que me hiciste un fanzine? Librería Dinova, septiembre 2014 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- El viudo, Gonzalo Oyanedel, Futuro esplendor, num. 1 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Las aventuraa alcoholicas de Capitán Copete, Caos comics, n. 1 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Anarco-metafísica, Librería Dinova, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Dibujantes chilenos, colaborando con Dino Gnecco, Librería Dinova, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- La pester negra, Nicolás Pérez de Arce, La Calaquita, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- 3 1/2, Tomás Fernández Díaz, La Calaquita, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Las aventuras de Tachi y Samy, Kunza cómics (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Cuentos para leer a media tarde, Blanca Gamuj Yue, Kunza cómics, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Árbol del silencio, Austral, Kunza cómics (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Un chungungo en Bolivia, [Esteban Castillo], El Chungungo, Kunza cómics (Box 7, Folder 5)
- El encuentro, Esteban Castillo, El Chungungo, Kunza cómics, 2014 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- ¿Por qué caen las estrellas? Esteban Castillo G., El Chungungo, Kunza cómics (Box 7, Folder 5)
- ¡Todo el mundo la luna y el sol te lo recomiendan!, Kunza cómics, #1, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Marraqueta cumpleaños, Kunza cómics (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Intermporarl, Tachi, Kunza cómics (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Historias de cagón y confort, La historia de mojón, Arkímedes cómix, Ilícito, Kéxuxa el cómic (Box 7, Folder 6)
- ¡La venganza de los fanzines vivientes! Arkímedes cómix, Ilícito, Kéxuxa el cómic, 2014 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- El hombre ano, JPAG, Ilícito (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Captan Luz, Ilícito comics (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Prolapso magazine, Comic man, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Guerilla is photography from the trench, 10 issues (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Zobako de bolsillo, Yayo, septiembre, 2014; Zobako "la ruta del inti", Yayo, 2014 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Zobako de bolsillo, no 1-5 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Histeria de Chile, Yayo, noviembre 2014, Zobako (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Zóbako!! Antologías, enero 2010. Zóbako!! Especial terremoto, julio 2011 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Ornitorrinko zine, Brenda Gatica, Yayo, 2013 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  General
  Comes with CD
- Revista mocha, 20, callejera, Yayo, Pititore, Paulo Meyer, Diego Galvez, octubre, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Beibis, Rachel Harrison; Beibis, Ferocius, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Champaña, III, junio 2015 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Vostok; Fotos mías, Rachel Harrison, 2016 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Color zine, no text, cover with green leaves, 8 pp [rachel Harrison?] (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Las cosas que guardo, Belén Villarroel, Oveja negra (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Simbiosis, Belén Villarroel, Oveja negra, junio 2015 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Hombre gigante; Gigante, Belén Villarroel, Oveja negra, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- La revolución de los pinguinos: paquidermo o la emboscada pinguina, Juan Vásquez (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Movimiento mapuche: cómic de resitencia, Juan Vásquez (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Pillan, fugitivo de la magia, Juan Vásquez, n. 1-2 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Adentro, Marino, Mar Eyes (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Con todo mi sida, Clauda Rodriguez (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Manifesto horrorista, poesia travesti, Claudia Rogriguez (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Dislocación: un hueso duro de roer colectiva, enero 2016 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Matamoscas, 4, diciembre 2013; Matamoscas mayo 2015 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Lucerna comics, n.1-2, Lira, Lynuz, Luis Volke, Felipe Choque, 2014-2015 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- El coleccionista; Detritus, Sebastián González Ruiz, diciembre 2015 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Visiones de noska, no. 5, Sebastián González Ruiz (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Black and white 3D booklet with bird on the cover. Includes sheet of stickers and set of 8 stickers, Perroseco (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Nuestra historia, julio 2015; [no title] blue booklet with boy and bear on the cover, noviembre 2015, Manuel Uloa, Feli (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Turno de noche, Rodolfo Castillo Lira, julio 2015 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Revista ayurame: revista periódica recopilatoria de cómics, abril 2016 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Historias del rock & roll, Crossroads, Kobal, Coyote, marzo 2016 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Minero34, Min34ro, diciembre 2015 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Siete embrujos ilustrados (de una duena de casa), Romina Ortega Mella (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Folla (G), n. 1, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Super fideos: RJ-45, Asertijo, el mundo deloso (Box 8, Folder 13)
- El nino que queria volar, Asertijo (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Dibujante en paro, el show debolita (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Space corneta, Butzbo, Mister paint (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Yogurt de pajaritos (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Inktober, Constanza Yovaniniz, 2015 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Brp!, por Arseniko, no. 1 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- No title. Cover shows woman's hand with cigarette, black and while, Distropico (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Sin huesos,Toros, n. 2, septiembre 2001 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- The evil ojenok, Deviant art, tomo 1 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Thrash no shadow, Ricky Crash comic man (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Que son los horribles? (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Grotesk book, Kendron Toqueen, 2016 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Toqueen octobook, Kendron Toqueen, 2016 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Manifesto vampiro, La peculiar historia de Misael Jakob el Vampiro Judio, Folkomics (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Sin huesos, Toro, n. 2, septiembre 2001 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Soy una gordita coqueta y golosa, Josefina Echevenia Lallane (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Winter mini sketchbook, Paulinaapc (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Limite, Catalina Rosas, junio 2015 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Figurama, la revista de: nadaserio, Felipe Venegas, Cristian Garcia, no.1- 2, 2015-2016 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- No debes huir nube, Jendalia (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Prision contrarada, Jendalia, abril 2016 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Wonder, A. Shitsuji (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Catalago fanzine oteca, 2012-2016 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Aun, Cayo la teja (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Rutina, Cayo la teja (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Historia de un pedacito de lapiz, Cayo la teja (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Espere su turno (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Frugalidad, Cayo la teja (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Libro cartoonero, Cayo la teja (Box 9, Folder 11)
- A cuadritos hazme la vida, Cayo la teja (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Tardes buena tenga usted, Costalazo ediciones (Box 9, Folder 12)